Inventory of the Carter Family Papers 1667-1862
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- People Files, 1667-1862. (Folder 1-102)
  - Carter, (Robert W.) 1792-1861; 1803-1862, n.d. (Folder 20-101)
    - Letters, 1803-1861. (Folder 20-50)
      - Letters, 1843-1844., 64 items. (Folder 31)
        - William H. Hill, at Sabine Hall, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 1 Aug 1843., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - L. Pierce to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Virginia, 16 Aug 1843., 1 item. (Folder 31)
          Postmarked Kilmarnock, Virginia
        - John T. Lomax, Jr., at Demopolis, [Ala.], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, Oct 3 1843., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - William C. Beale, at Fredericksburg, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond [County], 24 Oct 1843., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - G. Garner, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 30 Oct 1843., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - William C. Beale, at Fredericksburg, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Richmond [County], 4 Nov 1843., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - W. A. Spence, Jr., at Westmoreland Court House, Virginia, to Col.Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 4 Nov 1843., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - E. B. Stephens, at Warsaw, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Warsaw, 16 Nov 1843., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - Mace Clements, at Bladensfield, [Richmond County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 10 Jan 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - E. Conway, at Fredericksburg, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Richmond, 30 Jan 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - John M. McCarty, at Leesburg, [Loundoun County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, 3 Feb 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - John S. Corbin, Hanover County, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, 7 Feb 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - L. N. Carter, at Washington, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, [via] Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 22 Feb 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - Thomas H. Hunton, Northumberland County, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 18 April 1844., 1 item. Mutilated. (Folder 31)
        - John N. Doggett, at Ruther Glen, Caroline [County], to Robert W. Carter, Richmond Court House, Virginia, 10 May 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - Thomas H. Hunton, Northumberland County, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 10 June 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - Boyd Rust, [and others], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hill, 14 June 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
          [Letter requesting Col. Carter to deliver a Fourth of July oration at a place not specified].
        - Robert B. Jett, at Louisville, [Westmoreland County], to Col. Robert Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 10 July 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - John B. Brasham to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Virginia, 11 July 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
          Postmarked Litwalton, [Lancaster County], Virginia
        - E. Conway, at Fredericksburg, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, 16 July 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - W.M.M. Crabb to Col. Robert W. Carter, 23 July 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - E. Conway, at Fredericksburg, to R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 26 July 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - Newton Hill, cat Richmond,, to Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 10 Aug 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - F. W. Pendleton, at Farnham, [Richmond County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, 27 Aug 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - George W. Lewis, William Hutt, and Millo Newton, (Committee of Clay Club of Westmoreland County), at Westmoreland Court House, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 30 Aug 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - R. Edmond, at Indian Creek, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Richmond Court House, Virginia, 19 Sept 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - E. Conway, at Fredericksburg, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Richmond County, 5 Oct 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - Benjamin Ogle Tayloe, at Was[hington], to Col. Carter, 18 Nov 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - John Critcher, at Waterview, [Middlesex County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond Court House, Virginia, 22 Nov 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - G. W. Lewis, at Claymont, [Westmoreland County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, 25 Nov 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - David C. Tayloe, at Warsaw, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 5 Dec 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - John Robinson, at Warsaw, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 6 Dec 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - W. L. Weathers, at Warsaw, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, 6 Dec 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - R. W. C[arter] to Mrs. [?] Tayloe, 12 Dec 1844., 1 item. Copy. (Folder 31)
        - Landon C. Berkeley, at Aylette, King William County, to Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 16 Dec 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - J. Minor, at Fredericksburg, Virginia, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 17 Dec 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
        - Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, to D. C. Taylor, Westmoreland [County], 23 Dec 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
          Note: A statement of account appears on the same sheet.
        - G. W. Lewis, at Claymont, [Westmoreland County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 26 Dec 1844., 1 item. (Folder 31)
      - Letters, 1845., 60 items. (Folder 32)
        - Benedict Clarke, at Poplar Hill, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 2 Jan 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - B. Brinnon, at Mangorike, [Richmond County], to Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, 7 Jan 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Samuel Gresham, at Lancaster Court House, to Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 8 Jan 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - John Hooff, at Alexandria, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, 8 Jan 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Augustin Neale, at Shandy Hall, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, 9 Jan 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - George W. Goldsby, at Warsaw, Virginia, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 10 Jan 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - W. White, at Spring Grove, near Goodalls P. O., Hanover [County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 10 Jan 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Willoughby Newton, at Washington, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 11 Jan 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - W. C. Eustace, at Wingville, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 13 Jan 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
          Note: Mention is made of the burning of Mt. Airy.
        - Fanny D. Tomlin, at Wingville, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 15 Jan 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - John F. B. Jeffries, at Warsaw, to Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, 20 Jan 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
          Note: A statement is added to the letter showing mortgages given by John Critcher to various persons.
        - B. Brinnon, at Mangorike, [Richmond County], to Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, 23 Jan 1845., 1 item. Mutilated. (Folder 32)
        - Thomas L. Sydnor, at Heathsville, [Northumberland County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 23 Jan 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Ralph Edmond, at Indian Creek, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 27 Jan 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Richard L. T. Beale, at Cabinford, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, Jan 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Thomas L. Sydnor to Col. Robert W. Carter, 1 Feb 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - John F. B. Jeffries, at Warsaw, [Richmond County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, 7 Feb 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
          Note: Reference is made to the burning of Mount Airy.
          Enclosure: A copy of a court order giving nominations for sheriff of Richmond County. 1844.
        - J. A. Carter, at Crednall, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 8 Feb 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Carter Mitchell, at Wilna, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 8 Feb 1845., 1 item. Mutilated. (Folder 32)
        - B. Brinnon, at Mangorike, to Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, 13 Feb 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Augustin Neale, at Shandy Hall, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 9 March 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Wortham McGruder 4 Co., at Richmond, to Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 10 March 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, to C. G. Griswold, at Richmond, Virginia, 22 March 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Augustin Neale, at Shandy Hall, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 23 March 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, to B. D. Rust, 25 March 1845., 1 item. Two drafts of a letter. (Folder 32)
        - Thomas Jordan, at Tappahannock, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 27 March 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Thomas C. Braxton, at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert W. Carter, Richmond County, Virginia, 3 April 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
          Postscript by Maria G. Braxton.
        - J. A. Carter, at Alexandria, D. C., to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 16 April 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Robert L. Armistead, at Burnside, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond Court House, Virginia, 9 May 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - W. A. Spence, Jr., at North End, Mathews County, Virginia, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Virginia, 29 May 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - J. A. Carter, at Crednal, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine hall, near Warsaw, Virginia, 31 May 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Robert L. Armistead to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 6 June 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Edward T. Tayloe, at Powhatan Hill, [King George County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Virginia, 10 June 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Joseph Wheelwright, at Kinsale, [Westmoreland County], to Robert W. Carter, at Richmond Court House, 16 June 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - J. A. Carter, at Crednal, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Virginia, 19 June 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Fourth of July Committee, consisting of J. M. Stiff and others, at Farnham Church, [Richmond County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, 30 June 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Augustin Neale, at Shandy Hall, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 30 June 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
          Accompanying remarks by Robert W. Carter.
        - Norborn E. Sutton, at Richmond, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Richmond Court House, Richmond County, 3 July 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
          Forwarded to Warsaw.
        - C. G. Griswold, at Richmond, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 22 July 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - John S. Corbin, at Old Church Post Office, Hanover County, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 30 July 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Elizabeth L. Carter, at Washington, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 4 Aug 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Elizabeth Landon Carter, at Washington, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 11 Aug 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - R. L. Armistead to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 15 Aug 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Jane Steers, at Fort Mifflin, [Pennsylvania], to Robert W. Carter, at Washington, 13 Sept 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - S. Sprigg, at Baltimore, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Washington, D. C., 16 Sept 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
          Original letter and duplicate. The duplicate is addressed to Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia
        - Atterzon Clarke, at Warsaw, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Washington, 19 Sept 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - S. Sprigg, at Baltimore, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Washington, D. C., 22 Sept 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Adams & Co., at Baltimore, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Virginia, 25 Sept 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - S. Sprigg, at Baltimore, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Washington, D. C., 25 Sept 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - W. A. Spence, Jr., to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Warsaw, Virginia, 29 Sept 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Jane Steers, at Fort Mifflin, [Pennsylvania], to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 30 Sept 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Central Committee on Education, at Richmond, to Robert W. Carter, at Richmond Court House, Sept 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Edward T. Tayloe, at Powhatan Hill, [King George County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Virginia, 3 Oct 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Adams & Co., at Baltimore, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Warsaw, Virginia, 8 Oct 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - John S. Corbin to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Warsaw Post Office, Richmond County, Virginia, 10 Nov 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - T. Hunter, at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, 14 Nov 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - Robert Wellford, at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 27 Nov 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - J. A. Palmer, at Clifton, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 25 Dec 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - J. A. Parker, at Tappahannock, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Warsaw, R[ichmond] County, 26 Dec 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
        - W. C. Eustace, at Wingville, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Richmond County, 29 Dec 1845., 1 item. (Folder 32)
      - Letters, 1846., 36 items. (Folder 33)
        - Augustin Neale, at Shandy Hall, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 10 Jan 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Augustin Neale, at Shandy Hall, to Col. [Robert W. Carter], 13 Jan 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - W. A. Spence, Jr., Mathews County, Virginia, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Warsaw, Virginia, 29 Jan 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Edward T. Tayloe, at Powhatan Hill, [King George County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Virginia, 29 Jan 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Mary B. Carter, at Alexandria, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Warsaw, 30 Jan 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - John S. Corbin, at Old Church Post Office, Hanover County, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 1 Feb 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Edward T. Tayloe, at Powhatan Hill, [King George County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Virginia, 6 Feb 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Mary B. Carter, at Alexandria, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Warsaw, 7 Feb 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - R. W. C[arter], at Sabine Hall, to J. S. Corbin, 7 Feb 1846., 1 item. Copy. (Folder 33)
        - J. W. D. Ford, at Fredericksburg, to Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw P. O., Virginia, 11 Feb 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - John S. Corbin, at Old Church Post Office, Hanover County, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 16 Feb 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Mary B. Carter to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Warsaw, 8 March 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Benjamin Ogle Tayloe, at Washington, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Warsaw, Virginia, 2 April 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - C. G. Griswold, at Richmond, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 8 April 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Edward T. Tayloe, at Powhatan Hill, [King George County], to Col. R. W. Carter, at Warsaw, Virginia, 20 April 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - James A. Palmer, at Clifton, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 30 April 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Edward T. Tayloe, at Powhatan Hill, [King George County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, 10 June 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Augustin Neale, at Shandy Hall, to Col. Robert W. Carter, near Warsaw P. O., 15 June 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - R. L. Armistead to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 19 June 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - John R. Thompson, at Richmond, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Virginia, 2 July 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - C. G. Griswold, at Richmond, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 8 July 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Eliza Dorney, at Lidsville, to Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Westmoreland County [sic], 10 July 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Jane Steers, at Baltimore, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, Postmarked 13 July 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Jane Steers, at New York, to Mr. Carter, 27 July 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - E. Conway, at White Sulphur Springs, Greenbrier [County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw P. Office, Richmond County, Virginia, 31 July 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - David Pitts, at Loyds, Essex County, Virginia, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 21 Sept 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - E. Conway to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, 8 Oct 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - J. A. Parker, at Tappahannock, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 8 Oct 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - E. Conway, at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 13 Oct 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Virginia, to J. S. Skinner, 6 Nov 1846., 1 item. Copy. (Folder 33)
        - William H. Tayloe [to Robert W. Carter], 6 Nov 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Two letters written on the same page, Jan - Nov 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
          Two letters written on the same page:
          William H. Tayloe, at Mount Airy, [Richmond County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 6 Nov 1846.
          O. P. Hare, at Richmond, to William H. Tayloe, 1 Jan 1846.
        - J. H. Carter, Sr., at Centreville P. O., Fairfax County, Virginia, to Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw P. O., Richmond County, Virginia, 9 Nov 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - W. C. Eustace, at Wingville, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Richmond County, 9 Nov 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Robert Y. Conrad, at Winchester[?], to Col. Carter, 22 Nov 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
        - Augustin Neale, at Shandy Hall, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 23 Dec 1846., 1 item. (Folder 33)
      - Letters, 1847., 45 items. (Folder 34)
        - John H. Harding, at Clover Dale, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 12 Jan 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - Edward T. Tayloe, at Powhatan Hill, [King George County], to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Virginia, 21 Jan 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - Samuel Gresham, at Richmond, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 27 Jan 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - William H. Tayloe, at Walnut Grove, to Col. Carter, at Warsaw, Virginia, 6 Feb 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - Edward T. Tayloe, at Powhatan Hill, [King George County], to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Warsaw, Virginia, 19 Feb 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - John Belcher, at Richmond, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 2 March 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - P. R. Johnson, at Baltimore, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 7 March 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - Samuel Gresham, at Richmond, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 11 March 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - N. B. & C. B. Hill, at Richmond, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 13 March 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - James H. Lynch, at Richmond, to R. W. Carter, at Warsaw P. Office, Richmond County, Virginia, 25 March 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - William H. Tayloe, at Walnut Grove, to Col. Carter, at Warsaw, Virginia, 25 March 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - Thomas H. Hunton, Northumberland County, Virginia, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 4 April 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - Edward T. Tayloe, at Powhatan Hill, [King George County], to R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Virginia, 15 April 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - Christopher Hergeshimer, Richmond County, to Col. Carter, 18 April 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - John Belcher, at Richmond, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 25 April 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - Josiah Lee, at Baltimore, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Warsaw, Virginia, 28 April 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - Robert B. Sydnor, at Warsaw, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 12 May 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - William H. Tayloe, at Mount Airy, [Richmond County], to Col. R. W. Carter, 12 May 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - Robert W. Carter to Dr. John Mayo, at Warsaw, Virginia, 13 May 1847., 1 item. Copy. (Folder 34)
        - C. G. Griswold, at Richmond, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 22 May 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - J. A. Carter, at Crednal, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Virginia, 1 June 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - Samuel M. Lyell to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Virginia, 7 June 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - Robert B. Sydnor to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 12 June 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - H. T. Garnett, Jr., at King George Court House, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, 18 June 1847., 1 item. Printed Circular. (Folder 34)
        - William P. Taylor to Col. Robert Carter, at Richmond Court House, Virginia, 23 June 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - E. Conway, at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 8 July 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - John L. Marye, at Fredericksburg, to Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, 16 July 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - William H. Tayloe to Col. Carter, 20 July 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - William H. Tayloe, at Mount Airy, [Richmond County], to Col. [Carter], 21 July 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - William H. Tayloe, at Mount Airy, [Richmond County], to Col. [Robert W. Carter], 21 July 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - Jane Steers to Robert W. Carter, 28 Aug 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - Richard H. Carter, at Glen Welby, Fauquier County, Virginia, to Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw P. 0., Richmond County, Virginia, 20 Sept 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - Thomas D. Mutter, at Philadelphia, to [Robert W. Carter], 7 Oct 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - M[ary] L. Eliason, at Alexandria, to her brother [Robert W. Carter], 9 Oct 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
          Note: This letter is written on a printed circular of Mrs. Mary L. Eliason's Boarding and Day School for Young Ladies, Alexandria, Virginia
        - R. W. C[arter] to [?], 21 Oct 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)
        - W. Y. Sturman to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 23 Oct 1847., 1 item. (Folder 34)